Privacy policy
==============

StudyDaddy.com, founded and operated by StudyDaddy, has developed the following Privacy Policy with a view to helping users and visitors understand our ways of data collection and storage. Our Privacy Policy is designed to encourage you to make informed decisions when it comes to using our service located at StudyDaddy.com (hereinafter referred as “the Website”). When visiting or using the Website, you agree to follow all the rules listed in this Privacy Policy.

In case of an unresolved issue regarding privacy or personal information usage that was not addressed successfully, [contact us](https://studydaddy.com/contact-us).

Personally Identifiable Information
-----------------------------------

You can generally visit our Website without having to submit any personally identifiable information about yourself to us.

If you set up an account with us on the Website, we will collect personally identifiable information that you include in the registration or submission form, such as your email address, profile photo and username. If you set up an account with us on the Website, post a question or answer or other information in our Website, we will collect any personally identifiable information that you include in your submission or posting.

If you contact us with questions or request information we will collect your email address and any other personally identifiable information that you voluntarily transmit with your communications to us.

Information we collect as you browse our website
------------------------------------------------

The statistical data our webserver collects as you browse the website includes information about your IP address, the type of browser you are using, your operating system, and access times. Sometimes, cookies can be used to customize the content of our webpages, based on your browser type, IP address, or other anonymous information.

About cookies
-------------

Cookies are text files used to identify a computer to a server. Cookies identify which computer is being used, not a specific individual user. This tool is used by many different websites to monitor visitor traffic. Cookies gather information about areas of a website that users visit, and the time spent on a particular page. On our Website, cookies are used to serve the following functions:

* To remember that a user is in the process of making an order.
* To remember that a user is signed in.
* To display the date and time in accordance with the user's timezone.
* To improve user experience and make website navigation more convenient.

Users can modify browser settings to accept all cookies to receive a notification every time a cookie is used, or not to receive cookies at all. In case of the last option, the user might not be able to use some personalized services.

Usage of the Collected Data
---------------------------

On some webpages, you may be asked to provide some personal information, including your e-mail address. Please note that such information is never sold, rented or shared with any third party. We employ your information in these ways:

* Service supply and order completion
* Account administration
* Confirmation sending
* Sharing service updates along with a requested product
* Improving customer service
* Sharing significant updates
* Handling your inquires and concerns
* Modifying our marketing communications and the Website
* Conducting research and analyzing results

### Opt-Out

Users willing to unsubscribe from our newsletters and other marketing materials can do so by following the instructions provided in the aforementioned emails. If for some reason, you are unable to do it, [contact us](https://studydaddy.com/contact-us). We strongly recommend our users to create profiles and fill them in with the required information, i.e. photos, descriptions, etc. However, we don’t take any responsibility regarding the actions of users who you decided to share your information with. When registering at the Website, every user creates a personal account. So, their usernames and emails are automatically attached to the documents/programs/pictures they upload. Note that any other personal details are not provided to third parties.

### Disclosure of Your Personal Data

We reserve the right to disclose your personal information to third parties under certain circumstances described in this Privacy policy. We never share, sell, trade or distribute your individual info to other parties for promotional purposes. However, we might transfer your personal data to our service providers, partners and affiliates who assist us in our business operations, i.e. order delivery or handling customer requests. Such entities are authorized to access your information only when it is necessary to provide the needed services.

There are several other cases when we may disclose personal information of our users:

* Whenever it is required by law in order to comply with the rules and regulations;
* Whenever the disclosure is necessary to protect the rights and safety of our company; investigate a fraudulent action or fulfill a request from the government;
* Whenever the company is involved into mergers and acquisitions that lead to a sale of its assets, we notify our users via email or by posting a note at the Website;
* Whenever you grant us your consent for information disclosure.

The company can share your individual details with entities to help them better market their products to you. If you find this disturbing or unacceptable, please notify us via our email. Please remember that in order to successfully complete all the transactions, we disclose some of your personal details to users you transact with via our Website.

### Links

When browsing the Website, you may notice links to other web pages. The Website cannot be liable for the privacy approaches accepted at those pages. Therefore, we encourage you to stay alert whenever you leave our Website. Make sure to read privacy policy sections of other sites in order to learn how they collect and store your information. This Privacy policy in particular refers only to StudyDaddy.com.

### Personal Data and Your Rights

StudyDaddy respects and complies with the EU General Data Protection Regulations.

You have a right to be informed of Personal Data processed by Website, to request access to the information we have on you, a right to rectification/correction, erasure and restriction of processing.

You also have the right to receive from Website a structured, common and machine-readable format of Personal Data you provided to us.

If you believe the information we have about you is incorrect, you are welcome to contact us so we can update it and keep your data accurate. If you have any questions or comments, or if you want to update, delete, or change any Personal Data we hold, or you have a concern about the way in which we have handled any privacy matter, please use our [contact form](https://studydaddy.com/contact-us) to send us a message. You may also contact us by email at: [\[email protected\]](https://studydaddy.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

### Modifying Account Information

Users have a right to change, remove or edit information at their accounts whenever they find it necessary. All that is required to do is to log into your Account page, make changes and save those. The updates will instantly show up. You are also welcome to contact us so we can update your information.

### Information Security

All the necessary measures are taken to ensure the highest level of protection for users’ information. We store account detail on a protected server. Due to the fact that chat messages are not considered to be secure, we recommend you to send private details by private massages.

Information security is a top priority for us. Whenever you are asked to provide sensitive details, i.e. credit card information, you can be safe in knowledge that all the data is secured. We use the latest technologies to encrypt every transaction.

There are general standards of information protection that we always follow in our operations. Every transaction is protected at all stages, from entering personal data to completing a payment. Whether you want to know more about security or have questions, contact us via email [\[email protected\]](https://studydaddy.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

### Retention of Your Information

We can retain your personal data as long as you are using our service whilst keeping your account active. If you decide to delete your account or ask us to remove all your information from our database, contact our administrators.

### Signing Up with Other Services

Users can utilize other sign-in services, i.e. Facebook, to log in to the Website. By doing so, you allow the chosen service to identify you and provide this information to the Website. You will be asked for your email and name in a pop-up form. Please provide those to complete the log-in process. When using sign-in services, you get an option of posting any info at your profile page and share it via the chosen network.

### Unauthorized accounts

We remove any unauthorized accounts; therefore, if you notice any – please contact us.

### Modifications in the Privacy Policy

In case we make changes to the current privacy policy, we will place a notice to the Current Page and other pages we find appropriate. In addition, we may send out an email alert so that you get full information about modifications, reasoning behind those and guidelines if necessary.

We keep the right to make changes to this Privacy Policy at any time. Therefore, it is solely your responsibility to read it and learn about any modifications.

### Restrictions Regarding the Age

If your age is under 13 years old, under no circumstances can you visit the Website and use our service. If we find out that people under 13 y.o. use the Website and we have already collected their information, due measures will be taken and such information will be deleted.

Last Update: May 10th, 2018

Copyright © 2024 [StudyDaddy.com](https://studydaddy.com/)

Worbert Limited - All right reserved.  
20 Christou Tsiarta Elma 2, 22, 1077, Nicosia, Cyprus
